Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Office of the General President records, 1883-2001 IBT0017
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Office of the General President records
1883-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0017
4.25 Linear Feet
This collection contains materials produced by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Office of the General President. Included are IBT Constitutions and Community Service Surveys. These materials date from 1883-2001.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2012, [2012.021, 2012.025].
Arrangement
Organized into three series: Constitutions, Community Service Surveys, and Vice President's Papers
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials produced by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Office of the General President. Included are IBT Constitutions and Community Service Suyveys. These materials date from 1883-2001.
Biographical / Historical
The General President supervises the affairs of the union in accordance with the Constitution and is subject to review by the General Executive Board. The General President presides over the IBT Convention which is held every five years. There have been ten General Presidents to date. Ten staff departments report to the Office of the General President. The office of the General President is responsible for enforcing and maintaining the IBT Constitution. Changes to the Constitution are suggested and voted on by delegates to the IBT Convention.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Labor
- Constitutions, 1883-2001; Series 1; 1 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  The materials in this series include the constitutions of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America in booklet form. The dates range from 1886-2001. Each booklet contains the constitution and bylaws (internal rules and regulations) of the Teamsters Union. Over time the constitution and bylaws are amended and become more extensive as the organization grows in size.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically
  - Constitution, 1883 December 30; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, 1915 January 26; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constitution, 1925 December 1; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constitution, 1935 December 1; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constitution, 1938 January 12; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constitution, 1940 September 9-14; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Constitution, 1947 August 11-15; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitution, 1952 October 13-17; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Constitution, 1957 September 30 - October 5; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Constitution, 1960 May 19; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Constitution, 1961 July 3-7; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Constitution, 1962 June 27; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Constitution, 1966 July 4-7; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Constitution, 1971 July 5-8; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Constitution, 1981 June 1-5; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, 1981 June 1-5; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Constitution, 1986 May 19-23; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Constitution, 1991 June 24-28; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Constitution, 2001 June 25-29; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Constitution, 2011 June 27-July 1; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Community Service Surveys, 1963-1964; Series 2; 1.75 Linear Feet
  Arranged numerically by Local Union branch numbers.
  The materials in this series include the community service surveys from various local chapters of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America. The dates range from 1963-1964; all of the materials with the exception of one document are from 1963. The Surveys range from 1-4 pages with descriptions and sometimes photographs from the local chapter's involvement in charitable institutions. In the case that there were no charitable affiliations in the local branch a brief letter stating such is present.
  - Community Service Survey - General, 1963 April - August; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local 7 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Local 15 Community Service Survey, 1963 April 13; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Local 20 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 4; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Local 22 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local 22 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 24-25; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local 24 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local 28 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12-29; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Local 30 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 15; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Local 36 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 21; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Local 44 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local 50 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 21; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Local 53 Community Service Survey, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Local 64 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 16; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Local 64 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Local 79 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 14; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Local 81 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 30; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Local 81 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 3-7; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Local 87 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Local 89 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Local 90 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 9; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Local 95 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Local 96 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 23; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Local 100 Community Service Survey, 1963 October 7; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Local 103 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Local 104 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 23; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Local 106 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Local 110 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 23; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Local 110 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Local 116 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Local 119 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Local 126 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Local 141 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Local 144 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Local 145 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Local 150 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 8; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Local 153 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 23; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Local 162 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Local 164 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12 `; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Local 165 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Local 166 Community Service Survey, 1963 October 7; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Local 167 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Local 172 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 11; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Local 173 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 22; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Local 174 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Local 175 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Local 179 Community Service Survey, 1963 September; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Local 181 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Local 182 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Local 185 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Local 188 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 13; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Local 193 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Local 196 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Local 198 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Local 200 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Local 201 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Local 208 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Local 210 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 27; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Local 211 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Local 215 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Local 218 Community Service Survey, undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Local 221 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Local 226 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 7; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Local 229 Community Service Survey, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Local 232 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Local 236 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 20; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Local 239 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 28; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Local 240 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Local 245 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Local 247 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 24; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Local 257 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Local 259 Community Service Survey, 1964 January 28; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Local 263 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Local 265 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 14; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Local 267 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 11; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Local 285 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Local 287 Community Service Survey, 1963 November 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Local 288 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Local 289 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Local 294 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 23; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Local 295 Community Service Survey, 1963 April 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Local 297 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Local 300 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Local 301 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Local 302 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local 309 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local 311 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 24; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Local 312 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 16; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Local 315 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 27; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Local 317 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Local 319 Community Service Survey, Undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Local 327 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 16; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Local 328 Community Service Survey, 1963 March 19; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Local 329 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Local 331 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Local 334 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local 337 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 28; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local 340 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Local 342 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Local 343 Community Service Survey, Undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Local 344 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Local 352 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Local 359 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 6; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Local 364 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 25; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Local 368 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 6; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Local 377 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Local 378 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 2; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Local 379 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local 380 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 24; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Local 383 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Local 388 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 3; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Local 389 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 16; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Local 390 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Local 392 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 13; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local 393 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 16; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Local 395 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Local 397 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 6; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Local 402 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 21; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Local 404 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 22; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Local 405 Community Service Survey, 1963 may 27; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Local 406 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 18; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Local 407 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Local 408 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 4; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Local 409 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 18; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Local 413 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Local 414 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Local 421 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 1; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Local 422 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 13; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Local 426 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Local 428 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Local 430 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local 431 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 18; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Local 432 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Local 437 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 4; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Local 438 Community Service Survey, 1963 Auust 19; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Local 443 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Local 446 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Local 461 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Joint Council 36 (Local 464) Community Service Survey, 1963 August 27; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Local 467 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 25; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Local 471 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 21; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Local 473 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Local 483 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 13; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Local 485 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Local 487 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Local 490 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 20; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Local 493 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 28; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Local 496 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Local 497 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Local 498 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Local 512 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Local 517 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 10; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Local 523 Community Service Survey, 1963 October 29; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Local 526 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 11; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Local 542 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Local 546 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Local 552 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 21; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Local 555 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 16; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Local 556 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Local 564 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Local 566 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 16; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Local 567 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Local 568 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Local 569 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 11; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Local 572 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Local 574 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 28; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Local 581 Community Service Survey, 1963 October 23; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Local 592 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 2; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Local 595 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Local 600 Community Service Survey, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Local 612 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 20; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Local 615 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Local 619 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 6; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Local 627 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 6; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Local 628 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 24; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Local 631 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Local 637 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Local 638 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 9; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Local 643 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 22; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Local 647 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 22; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Local 648 Community Service Survey, 1963 November 1; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Local 653 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Local 657 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Local 662 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Local 664 Community Service Survey, 1963 February 6; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Local 668 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Local 670 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 28; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Local 673 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Local 675 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Local 676 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Local 678 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Local 679 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Local 680 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 23; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Local 682 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Local 686 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Local 690 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 30; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Local 695 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 25; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Local 699 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 24; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Local 703 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Local 706 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 4; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Local 711 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 2; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Local 712 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Local 714 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Local 716 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Local 725 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Local 726 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 21; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Local 728 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 24; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Local 729 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Local 731 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Local 734 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 11; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Local 738 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 14; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Local 741 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Local 743 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 29; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Local 745 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 14; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Local 750 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 18; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Local 754 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Local 761 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Local 762 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Local 764 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Local 765 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 12; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Local 767 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Local 776 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 23; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Local 780 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 2; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Local 782 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 21; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Local 784 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Local 787 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Local 789 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Local 792 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 30; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Local 794 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 9; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Local 804 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 9; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Local 808 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Local 809 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 12; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Local 813 Community Service Survey, Undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Local 818 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 16; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Local 822 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Local 823 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 26; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Local 830 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Local 838 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 2; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 36)